<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives - Flowcharts Effective Altruism</title>
	<atom:link href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://circle.seomonitor.com/category/news/</link>
	<description>Designed &#38; priced for agencies. Loved by in-house teams, too. · Rank Tracker · SEO Forecast · SEO Research · Organic Traffic · Agency Dashboard · API &#38; Integrations.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:11:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Construction of the second subway began in July</title>
		<link>https://circle.seomonitor.com/construction-of-the-second-subway-began-in-july/</link>
					<comments>https://circle.seomonitor.com/construction-of-the-second-subway-began-in-july/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://circle.seomonitor.com/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina will officially inaugurate the construction of the country&#8217;s second subway from Hemayetpur to Bhatara. Officials of Dhaka Mass Transit Company Limited are talking about the possibility of officially opening the second subway construction work in July. No date has been set yet. However, MRT Line 5 Northern Route work is progressing ... <a title="Construction of the second subway began in July" class="read-more" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/construction-of-the-second-subway-began-in-july/" aria-label="More on Construction of the second subway began in July">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/construction-of-the-second-subway-began-in-july/">Construction of the second subway began in July</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina will officially inaugurate the construction of the country&#8217;s second subway from Hemayetpur to Bhatara. Officials of Dhaka Mass Transit Company Limited are talking about the possibility of officially opening the second subway construction work in July. No date has been set yet. However, MRT Line 5 Northern Route work is progressing ahead of the opening of the construction work in July. In the meantime, the land acquisition and the registration of the acquired land have been completed, said the officials concerned.</p>
<p>The MRT Line 5 Northern Route project is underway to build a 20 km metro rail from Hemayetpur to Vatara by 2018. Out of the 20 km long route, 13.50 km of underground and 6.50 km of aerial infrastructure will be constructed. It will have 14 stations. Of these, nine are underground and five are airborne stations.</p>
<p>Officials say that the feasibility study and basic design of the MRT Line 5 Northern Route have already been completed. Detailed design work is in progress. As of April, the detailed design of the project has progressed to 80 percent. After the financial evaluation of the tender for the Hemayetpur Depot land development package, the consent of the donor agency JICA has also been received. It is currently in the process of being presented to the board meeting of DMDCL for approval.</p>
<p>About Tk 934.84 crore has been paid for the estimated amount of 99.25 acres land acquisition for construction of Hemayetpur Depot and Depot Access Corridor. The acquired land was taken over on October 3, 2022 and gazetted for 99.25 acres of land on October 20. In the meantime, land registration has been completed. The overall progress of land acquisition (Hemayetpur Depot) is 85% till the end of April.</p>
<p>Dhaka Mass Transit Company Limited Managing Director MAM Chiddik told Bangla Tribune that the construction work of MRT Line 5 Northern Route is likely to be inaugurated by the Honorable Prime Minister in July. The construction of aeronautical and underground stations will be carried out efficiently by studying all aspects.</p>
<p>Route Map of Northern Route</p>
<p>From Hemayetpur Depot to Baliarpur, Bilamalia, Aminbazar, Gabtali, Darus Salam, Mirpur 1, Mirpur 10, Mirpur 14, Kachukshet, Banani, Gulshan 2, New Bazar, Bhatara. There will be flying stations from Hemayetpur to Aminbazar. Then Gabtali will go underground through various routes to the new market. And connect by flying to Vatara.</p>
<p>Earlier, on December 28, 2022, Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina inaugurated the metro rail movement of MRT Line Six Metrorail from Uttara North to Agargaon.</p>
<p>Besides, on February 2 this year, Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina inaugurated the construction of the first underground metro rail MRT line 1 airport route and Purbachal route.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/construction-of-the-second-subway-began-in-july/">Construction of the second subway began in July</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://circle.seomonitor.com/construction-of-the-second-subway-began-in-july/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Galtier has been sacked by PSG</title>
		<link>https://circle.seomonitor.com/galtier-has-been-sacked-by-psg/</link>
					<comments>https://circle.seomonitor.com/galtier-has-been-sacked-by-psg/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://circle.seomonitor.com/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Christophe Gaultier could not keep his job after winning the French Ligue 1 title. French club Paris Saint-Germain (PSG) have cut him, ESPN reported. This season, PSG won Ligue 1 under him. But the club authorities decided to drop him as Champions League success was elusive. This time they had to leave after losing to ... <a title="Galtier has been sacked by PSG" class="read-more" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/galtier-has-been-sacked-by-psg/" aria-label="More on Galtier has been sacked by PSG">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/galtier-has-been-sacked-by-psg/">Galtier has been sacked by PSG</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Christophe Gaultier could not keep his job after winning the French Ligue 1 title. French club Paris Saint-Germain (PSG) have cut him, ESPN reported.</p>
<p>This season, PSG won Ligue 1 under him. But the club authorities decided to drop him as Champions League success was elusive. This time they had to leave after losing to Bayern Munich in the last sixteen.</p>
<p>PSG sporting director Luis Campos broke the news of Gaultier&#8217;s sacking himself on Tuesday, ESPN reported. The club authorities are continuing to negotiate with Bayern coach Julian Nagelsmann to replace him.</p>
<p>Citing sources, ESPN also reported that they have also spoken with former Spain and Barcelona coach Luis Enrique. But their main target is the Nagglesman. And the German coach wants Thierry Henry as his assistant.</p>
<p>Galtier joined PSG last summer after leading Nice to ninth place in the 2021-22 season. Before that he also worked at Lille, Saint Etienne.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/galtier-has-been-sacked-by-psg/">Galtier has been sacked by PSG</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://circle.seomonitor.com/galtier-has-been-sacked-by-psg/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaving Madrid is difficult: Benzema</title>
		<link>https://circle.seomonitor.com/leaving-madrid-is-difficult-benzema/</link>
					<comments>https://circle.seomonitor.com/leaving-madrid-is-difficult-benzema/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://circle.seomonitor.com/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many were surprised by Karim Benzema&#8217;s decision to leave. Even after that, it is difficult to accept the prediction. Real Madrid legend Karim Benzema feels the same way. The French forward said at his farewell ceremony on Tuesday that it was difficult for him to leave Real Madrid. Benzema was one of the holders of ... <a title="Leaving Madrid is difficult: Benzema" class="read-more" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/leaving-madrid-is-difficult-benzema/" aria-label="More on Leaving Madrid is difficult: Benzema">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/leaving-madrid-is-difficult-benzema/">Leaving Madrid is difficult: Benzema</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many were surprised by Karim Benzema&#8217;s decision to leave. Even after that, it is difficult to accept the prediction. Real Madrid legend Karim Benzema feels the same way. The French forward said at his farewell ceremony on Tuesday that it was difficult for him to leave Real Madrid.</p>
<p>Benzema was one of the holders of Real Madrid&#8217;s tradition for 14 years. He gave everything he needed to become a club legend. Said during his farewell, he wanted his career to end in Madrid. So why didn&#8217;t it happen? Explaining this, he said, &#8216;Today is a sad day. Because the club has to leave. It is difficult for me. I was working on a dream &#8211; to sign for Madrid, to end my career here. But life sometimes brings other opportunities.&#8217;</p>
<p>The event to officially say goodbye to Benzema was held at the training ground in Madrid. In his farewell speech, Cristiano Ronaldo&#8217;s former teammate said, &#8216;I will always watch Madrid&#8217;s matches even if I leave. And thanks to the audience, who motivated me to play well.&#8217;</p>
<p>At the end of his career, Benzema signed for Madrid in 2009. Before that he played for the French club Lyon. He played 648 matches for the Spanish club in these 14 years. Which is the second highest number of matches played for the club. Only Ronaldo is ahead of him. That teammate is going to be his rival in the Saudi League this time. The Portuguese star is playing for Al Nasr. And Benzema is going to Jeddah-based Al Ittihad on a three-year deal. He expressed his gratitude to Madrid President Florentino Perez during his farewell. He also said, &#8216;I will never forget Real Madrid. It is the best club in the world and history. But now it&#8217;s time to leave, to see another story.&#8217;</p>
<p>Perez also thanked Benzema at the farewell ceremony. Said, &#8216;Today is not just another player leaving. We are saying goodbye to one of the most incredible players in our history.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/leaving-madrid-is-difficult-benzema/">Leaving Madrid is difficult: Benzema</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://circle.seomonitor.com/leaving-madrid-is-difficult-benzema/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finally I Quit Smoking, Why You Should Too</title>
		<link>https://circle.seomonitor.com/finally-i-quit-smoking-why-you-should-too/</link>
					<comments>https://circle.seomonitor.com/finally-i-quit-smoking-why-you-should-too/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://circle.seomonitor.com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mom you&#8217;re going to die.&#8221; The number of times my son shook his head in horror when he saw me smoking pales in comparison to the arguments we had for smoking cigarettes. So I gave up. The time is 2019. Julia the Virgin. His son gave up smoking. To help others overcome this addiction, he ... <a title="Finally I Quit Smoking, Why You Should Too" class="read-more" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/finally-i-quit-smoking-why-you-should-too/" aria-label="More on Finally I Quit Smoking, Why You Should Too">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/finally-i-quit-smoking-why-you-should-too/">Finally I Quit Smoking, Why You Should Too</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mom you&#8217;re going to die.&#8221; The number of times my son shook his head in horror when he saw me smoking pales in comparison to the arguments we had for smoking cigarettes. So I gave up. The time is 2019.</p>
<p>Julia the Virgin. His son gave up smoking. To help others overcome this addiction, he shared his experience with the German media Deutsche Welle.</p>
<p>Julia said, &#8216;I quit smoking for two months. Never took it again. Dr. Tobias Ruther was thrilled that I had quit smoking. He heads the specialty outpatient clinic for tobacco addiction treatment at the Ludwig Maximilian University in Munich.&#8217;</p>
<p>Doctor Tobias told Julia, &#8216;When you quit smoking, you will see many positive things happen in your life.&#8217;</p>
<p>A lot of things will change soon<br />
Eight hours after you quit smoking, your body will take in a lot more oxygen, Tobias said. After a day or two, many smell and taste as before. After two weeks, lung function also increases, especially during sports.</p>
<p>After giving up smoking, Julia said that she feels as fit as ever.<br />
&#8216;After quitting smoking, you may have a lot of phlegm, which was not the case before,&#8217; says Tobias. This means that your lungs are clearing them out on their own. It may take up to a month to fully clear. And after this one month your immunity will increase a lot. When you read like this in three months, you will sleep well at night. Smokers experience nicotine deprivation even during sleep. But you won&#8217;t. You will sleep comfortably. After three months your sleep will be normal.&#8217;</p>
<p>The danger starts from the third cigarette<br />
Before quitting smoking completely, Julia Virgin thought that cutting back on cigarettes might not do much harm to health. But his idea was not entirely true. Because, more than two cigarettes are enough to harm health.</p>
<p>Dr. Tobias said that smoking between 3 and 20 cigarettes increases the risk of stroke and heart disease. However, cancer is different. In that case, that risk increases with each cigarette. However, one in two smokers die from tobacco addiction. And 50 percent of them died before the age of 70.</p>
<p>Julia said, &#8216;Tobias was sure I would feel the effects of smoking by the time I was 50. But it&#8217;s a huge achievement for me because I can really quit.&#8217;</p>
<p>95 percent go back<br />
Julia commented, &#8216;This addiction doctor felt that I didn&#8217;t need nicotine patches, hypnosis or acupuncture as medication to keep cigarettes off my hands. In this case my desire was the key. Even since I started smoking after I turned 21, that was a positive.&#8217;</p>
<p>Dr Tobias said most smokers start smoking between the ages of 12 and 16. Nicotine is a highly active neurotransmitter, which has a major impact on the development of neural connections in the brain. As a result, it becomes a lifelong addiction, which can rarely be overcome by sheer willpower.</p>
<p>It can be seen that 95% of those who give up their addiction by sheer force of will return to it within the first year of quitting.</p>
<p>A smoker&#8217;s obsession<br />
Julia said, &#8216;One of the reasons for returning to this bad habit after quitting smoking is the attraction or attraction of the smoker. This is a nasty psychological trick by nicotine. The doctor told me that psychological dependence is a strong factor behind cigarette addiction. I checked myself and found that it was. That&#8217;s why I also got addicted to smoking. For years I believed that smoking would calm me down, relieve stress and give me some measure of relief.&#8217;</p>
<p>The doctor said, &#8216;The reality is that every cigarette increases your heart rate and makes you more restless.&#8217;</p>
<p>Pavlov&#8217;s dog<br />
The first evening without cigarettes was quite strange with music and wine with friends. Nothing, it didn&#8217;t feel right to Julia. &#8220;For years, I&#8217;ve told myself that smoking is only part of certain moments, like with coffee, with wine, or on a break,&#8221; he says.</p>
<p>&#8216;It works like Pavlov&#8217;s dog,&#8217; says Dr Tobias. You gave the dog something to eat and at the same time rang a bell. Sometimes that hour is enough to make a dog salivate.&#8217;</p>
<p>For smokers, this bell rings permanently. After work, after eating, while waiting for the bus. The list goes on and on. The bottom line, Tobias said, is that cigarettes become part of smokers&#8217; daily lives.</p>
<p>You want to quit, but how?<br />
It becomes very difficult for a person who wants to quit smoking addiction. Tobias initially reassures his patients that failure is normal and part of quitting. &#8216;Every time a patient tells me they&#8217;ve tried to quit five times,&#8217; says Tobias. Then I welcome their initiative.&#8217;<br />
The doctor also said that quitting smoking is like learning to ride a bicycle. Falling is part of it. It is important to sit up.</p>
<p>At the same time, something has changed &#8211; this signal must be given to the brain. According to Tobias, &#8216;Sit in a different chair each day in the morning. Drink tea instead of coffee. Change the location of plants in the workplace.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com/finally-i-quit-smoking-why-you-should-too/">Finally I Quit Smoking, Why You Should Too</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://circle.seomonitor.com">Flowcharts Effective Altruism</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://circle.seomonitor.com/finally-i-quit-smoking-why-you-should-too/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
